OPEYEMI OLADUNJOYE

16, Silifat Abioye Street, Oke-Ira, Ogba, Lagos · +234 7061095032

Opeyemioladunjoye73@gmail.com

I am very passionate about research and technology. Although I have a little experience in design and development of web-based, client-server applications with some understanding of Object-Oriented programming using, JavaScript, CSS and HTML. I hope to gain more knowledge and experience in web based development and client-server based applications.

To provide myself with the necessary experience required in the pharmacy profession while also improving various pharmaceutical skills which include customer relationship/communication skills, knowledge of drugs and learning about modern pharmaceutical developments in the pharmacy profession.

EXPERIENCE

OCTOBER 2018 – FEBRUARY 2019, OCTOBER 2020- FEBRUARY 2021 LOCUM PHARMACIST, CIBETH PHARMACY LIMITED, AREPO, OGUN STATE

DECEMBER 2021 TILL DATE PRE-INTERN PHARMACIST, MATRIX PAHRMACY AND STORES, OMOLE PHASE 1, IKEJA, LAGOS STATE.

EDUCATION

2015-2021 B.PHARM, UNIVERSITY OF LAGOS, LAGOS STATE, NIGERIA (Second Class Upper Division)

SKILLS

- Solid knowledge of drug administration and health & safety guidelines
- Excellent understanding of pharmaceutical therapy and direct patient care
- Great knowledge of computers
- Knowledge of HTML, JAVASCRIPT AND CSS in building front-end portion of websites

JavaScript :

Objects, functions, strings, array, iteration, loop(for), numbers, date formats, booleans, date format, HTML dom(event listener, forms, navigation, elements), Asynchronous, callback function.

• HTML:

Attributes, headings formatting, elements, Id, file path, layout ,forms(attributes, input types, input form attributes), media(video, audio, plugin)

CSS:

Colors, background, height/width, padding, borders, box models, tables, lists, links, fonts, display, max-width, z-index, position, overflow, float, inline-block, align, pseudo-class, pseudo-element, website layout, navigation bar, border images ,2d-transform,3d-transform, transitions, animations, pagination, user-interface, media queries.

- Understanding of the use of HTML, JAVASCRIPT AND CSS in the creation of a user-interface.
- Aptitude in problem-solving and decisionmaking

OBJECTIVES

I have a huge passion for web development and understanding the different methods and techniques to ensuring the creation an optimal user - interface. I am a front-end developing starter with the basic skills needed but with a greater desire to know more about the profession.